when you think about the first time we
met what do you remember I remember and
just being amazed at how kind your eyes
were like honestly it was just but I've
always kind of thing about that what
that was and then you know the fact that
you kept forgetting me obviously that's
from that day that's one of the things
that I just remember thinking that he
smiles with his eyes and there are the
kindest eyes I've ever seen you know you
know this guy what do you love about our
relationship
the fact that no matter what you're my
friend at the end of the day is we can
have good days bad days argue about
stupid stuff at the end of the day
you're my best friend I think that's
probably one of the most important
things to me it's the fact that you
truly are my friend you know you know
just my fuck buddy I never sugarcoat
anything do you know it's actually kind
of fun when do you feel closest to me
I'd have to say when probably when
you've been there me most the lowest
points where mama died you'll have to
let you know I think that's enough when
I'm at my lowest gonna be anything but
what are you hesitant to tell me nothing
absolutely nothing I think that's bull
no you know every little thing about my
life
before and after there's nothing that
you pause before you tell me or anything
like that there are things that wait and
if I feel like if something's going to
hurt your feelings I will pause but I
mean I never hold anything from you
there's no point it's Jo you talking you
sleep oh do we have enough sex no this
is a question every guy asks no then
ninety nine so that honestly and every
guy does probably ask it every single
one of our friends does I do not put out
enough I can tell you that right now but
I will say that let me do it is quality
and you know honestly I don't really
know that many people that have been
together as long as we have better still
even having as much sex as we have town
we know people that haven't touched each
other in years well I kind of know this
answer who has more power in the
relationship you or me
next question everyone knows answer that
you know you do you know it's all about
you I think I like to think I'm in
charge from time to time built on your
neck hey turn the head great what
bothered you about being the sole income
provider well that's actually more your
question since I'm really not that's
more than your question to answer I know
it makes me feel awkward and it makes me
feel then I'm not keeping up my end of
the bargain it's not exactly cheap I
live over here and stuff you know yeah
but I'll never understand what you think
like that because I've always had my own
job my own income been so completely
self-reliant that I took the past two
years have been really rough I mean I
really feel like I've lost part of my
identity
so not I got any the little strong more
like um know a little bit of the
security in who I was and who I am and
who I knew myself to be for so long and
especially because I was so in my career
the entire time that we've been together
that this is just a completely weird
misstep for me you know yeah everyone
has hard times and we're a couple so it
doesn't know
I know wow in the back of your mind are
you scared that I'll walk away
at times I think everyone thinks that I
haven't thought that but again a long
time ago
well we bid through I don't think it
anymore I did one time not anymore
my when things were tough back in the
day when I was let's be like barely
working it was hard it was really really
hard because I always felt like I was
not living up to your expectations
sort of like the way I feel now but
we've both been there and we've gotten
through everything right oh this is very
end up with the sex questions you guys
am I the best sex you've ever had
[Laughter]
already no it's no so that's terrible
this is this is bad no no no to say I'm
gonna gather for a very long time no to
say that it's not that it's you're not
the best sex I've ever had
well no I mean we've been together for
almost 20 years
no no I know but it's just it's so
awkward for me it's no secret we can
just name it I know why it's it's the
kind of thing where no but the type of
sex that we have is a different type of
sex than I've ever had with anyone else
so to just randomly compare it one it's
apples and oranges is obnoxious at that
you know yeah it's all fruit it's all
straight sex granted this you know
different flavors
but it's it's a completely it's a
different scenario it's not like I can
equally wear a moment the other but I
don't talk to you about this I don't
think we really do talk about this in
all the time that very rare we very rare
yeah like yeah no so that was kinda
interesting yeah wow that's terrible no
it's it did you ever want children with
me yes I don't even have to hesitate yes
how do you feel we've grown apart
I think the older that we are just we're
not as forgiving enough to write them in
the right words but I don't think that
we gave each other a lot of leeway with
certain subjects anymore like I'm not
gonna put up with you when you do
conservative Republican bullshit because
you know conservative Republican is
someone you say shit like that it really
drives me batshit and I won't put up
with any more and I tell you you know to
shut up I think in terms of stuff like
that but I don't think that we've really
grown apart in that way unless you are
saying like the whole sexually thing
which is again I just consider that
normal and I'm so that um you know I
don't felt like I'm 20 anymore I just we
you know what would you do if I cheated
on you
[Laughter]
something like honestly though I already
kind of know we can sort of go by this
one oh well this I would not be a happy
man
I just I just just because of the
history game one of those it's just not
something yeah don't you have to be
concerned about it I'm very into time
one who said before I start another no I
wouldn't do that
we both know each other better than that
what are you scared to tell me
when I fuck up bad I know it sounds old
or ridiculous but it's more it's more a
matter of it's not when I messed up so
much it's where I do something or I
don't do something or I procrastinate
about something to the point where I
think you're going to be disappointed in
me it's almost like I don't want to
disappoint you
you don't I mean it's not so it's not
like you know like be afraid to tell you
something it's just you know like going
out and drinking too much wine and
falling asleep in the cab on the way
home and losing my phone you know like
the same shit everybody does except you
know they did it fifteen years younger I
mean stuff like that it's it's more I
don't want to disappoint you and I don't
want to embarrass myself by being
immature but I kind of feel like no no
fuck it sometimes I'm gonna disappoint
you but you love me anyway
okay so it's not really like there's
nothing really that I'd be like afraid
talking about but hmm
do you feel like we've lived up to the
dreams we had when we started this
relationship why or why not I don't
think we've lived up to our potential
because well it's good to have you give
me a moment there's just been so many
things I've happened along the way with
family and everything and loss of jobs
and it's just it's hard sometimes when
it when you I thought by this time we we
don't know already it's just sometimes
just talking I think that's probably I
never really wanted the house no I never
would even even like I didn't want to
watch it but you know to have a space of
do you and I have a family you know be
like Auntie Mame you know like all that
I really wanted but it hasn't worked out
like that well it's it's not over yet
see your truth of mine I actually don't
go just go with us man was the biggest
compromise you've made I haven't
acknowledged
I don't think that don't think go into
that huh I just I don't think it's
anything that you haven't acknowledged
per se without delving into more of it I
think it's more you don't take it as
serious as I think I don't think you
realize how much it affects me
why do you love me I honestly I can't
even narrow that down why I I just don't
I can't have anything everything
everything that makes you you this corny
Sophie's that sounds it's just you what
do I do that detracts from our
relationship oh my god you become like
and eat your own boy and you have a
temper tantrum beg for Captain Crunch
because I left one sheet of paper towel
you're having an epic meltdown like I
was just like no you can't have the
boxes here fucking doing it like really
back Roy is probably that's up there
that's my hissy fits well and I mean
what is your question that might
in the time that we have shared together
do you have any resentment toward me
though see no I don't think that's true
why do you think that's true I think I
don't know so much now because you're in
a power position without sounding
amounts just I don't mean it like you
know like you mourn over me or anything
but relationship wise right now you're
in a power position and I think that
when I was still VP company and I was
devoting so much time to my career and
something that was so outside of us and
outside of our relationship and our
lives together I think that part of you
we not only resented me but that really
didn't like me as a person and I just
don't think that you like the person
that I was and I think that's also when
we probably had most of our discord and
the problems in our relationship I think
it was probably our worst point
especially the last like five years or
so there I think that you've resented
the amount of time I spent there how
much more I cared or appear to care
about well I don't think I wouldn't
advise that you resented the amount of
time you were giving that as opposed to
us because I felt like you were just
killing yourself with no reason for so
long you see why I would take away oh
absolutely absolutely
it's reason
still swimmin you what story Zeppelin
when do I hurt you when I'm trying to
lead you down the right path and you
just won't listen
and you know what I'm talking about
do you know exactly what I'm talking
about when I'm Quillan hurting myself I
try to just really back in if I can and
when you just don't even give me the
chance to explain their hurts me at
times but most of the time when I'm at
like to Adam thinking of you
list the top three best memories from
our relationship top three that's a long
time time you coming in Vinod pneumonia
and showing up with like the saddest
plastic bottle of watching the craft for
like 599 times and just hanging out with
me because I was so sick I would
definitely and we weren't even having
sex at that point you know but I'd say
that's definitely one and another one is
not necessarily a particular time but
and even though there's a picture of it
it's like a snapshot always in my head
and it's right there when we got married
and we had busted out all the glow
necklaces and it looks like just like
the one I even like you know just like
zoom in around a circle you were just
like you were having such a great time
it was like you were at your own rave oh
that is definitely up there and
[Music]
the tops it's not okay number of all
it's not like you know like it would
depend I would think like you know it
would probably be when we were on the
jet skis in Myrtle Beach
and seeing the dolphins and stuff you
know like you know like I'd say more so
than the squishy dolphin moment was the
air jaws moment when I nearly broke my
ass I'd say that guy in particular that
was a that was a great day that really
was what we do is baby you know it's
hard to think I'm just doing who what do
we care for me it's it's not about the
day it's about a moment like for me it's
like when I get to just see pure joy on
your face like just only two years ago
one of my favorite moments with you was
the first time we went fishing together
you would never look see I have never
seen you smile so hard and you know
that's just a woman it was just an
amazing day that wasn't about the entire
day it was about just looking at you at
that moment
I'll take it hard it's it's nice it's
nice how do you feel that I always rope
you in to stuff like this like I just do
you ever feel that sometimes my
adventurous side in terms of just doing
something that we would never do does
that every irritate you that more
free-spirited than you are in that way
no I'll take it rotates me at all I kind
of enjoy it actually because you're like
crazy right you'd never know what's
gonna happen you know there's that one
day we're sitting the concept you know
hey you're not having a sex no but what
I mean is it's never done it's never
done
well one day you're you're making
pickles your next day today we're gonna
go shoot this video all right sure
whatever you're going on game or can't
really suck that bad right here
have you ever wanted to live anywhere
outside of New York like in terms of
could you picture yourself living
anywhere outside of the five boroughs or
even outside of Manhattan Brooklyn she
this point in the moment now or just in
general like there are times that I just
think that I don't I don't feel that I
would be comfortable in my own skin
anywhere else I don't know if it's from
and I don't know if I wouldn't feel
accepted I think that there's a certain
amount of leeway that living here gives
you it's a sort of feel you're eccentric
yes you know what I mean like I don't
think I'd be able to be like this in
Boone Iowa or like you know everybody is
not extremely having this that's what I
mean like even though I have family in
the Midwest and even though I have
family scattered all over the place
really have never pictured myself living
truly anywhere else ever I found will I
like to or yeah just for us in the
future or is it something that you can
see yeah I mean absolutely right now
though the way things are and I haven't
have security here right now but in the
near future you know nearer to I like to
move yeah absolutely
[Music]
some place definitely morning
oh I feel like I should be asking more
questions
hmm is there anything that you wanted to
ask that now I'm on the spot
hmm yeah actually there do you think if
your mother was still here we would
still be one family you don't have to
answer because I miss it I miss
everybody I think that uh I think that
uh mommy kept us together she's the only
mother I had and family and part of the
reason why we're is part is why were as
fragmented killer yeah it's because she
really help us together she was the rock
I really okay it's okay all right
yeah it's good you know you have to say